virginhealthmiles.com 2015-09-29

# Privacy Policy - Virgin Pulse

Virgin Pulse (“Virgin Pulse”) is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains what we can and cannot do with the information we collect about you and what steps you can take to protect that information.

To enable us to provide quality service to our members, we need to keep personal information about you, including information about your health, fitness and related activities, your email address, and your credit card number (“Personal Information”). This information will be collected through the Virgin Pulse measurement stations as well as information you provide through our Web site. In addition, we will collect non-personal information related to your use of our Web site through the Internet (e.g., cookies).

If you are a member, the Personal Information we collect will be used to track your fitness progress, determine your points for the reward program, as well as to provide you with information that you may find helpful. Virgin Pulse staff may also access your Personal Information to contact you regarding your participation in a Virgin Pulse program.

You will have access to some of your Personal Information on the measurement stations and all your Personal Information via our Web site. If any of your Personal Information is inaccurate or outdated, you can correct it at any time on the Web site.

Virgin Pulse will de-identify your information and disclose it in combination with others’ information in such a way that no one could trace the information back to you directly (i.e. anonymous, aggregated data). This anonymous, aggregated data may be shared with other organizations for research purposes. You are welcome to request the names of such organizations from us.

If you became a member of Virgin Pulse through your employer’s participation in one of our programs, then we will supply your employer with the same anonymous, aggregated data mentioned above. Your employer will not be able to trace such information directly back to your identity. Your employer may use this information to provide additional benefits, programs and services.

Your Personal Information will not be sold, divulged, or made available to any third party without your permission except as set forth in this policy or when Virgin Pulse has a legal duty to make the information available to a legally authorized party. However, we may distribute such information to our partners, affiliates and subsidiaries so that we may better serve your needs. Such information collaboration with third parties includes these limited circumstances:

  * We have received your consent (we require express consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information);
  * To assist with our marketing activities, such as, direct mailers, webinars, online notifications, and distribution of promotional offers.
  * To our insurers, auditors, and attorneys, on a need-to-know basis;
  * In the event of a merger, acquisition, debt financing, or any form of sale of all or part of company assets or other event in which personally identifiable information could be transferred to third parties as part of our company’s business assets.

We require that third parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

In addition, we may share personal information to access, use, preserve or disclose such personal information as reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable terms of service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Virgin Pulse, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.

Should you decide to end your Virgin Pulse membership, we will de-identify your Personal Information.

Virgin Pulse has taken responsible measures to ensure that no unauthorized person can obtain access to your Personal Information. Among the security measures taken are a login process requiring a password and username that you select and a firewall protecting our hosting server. Virgin Pulse will retain your password and username as part of your Personal Information, but will not share this information with anyone. Please be advised that you are responsible for keeping your password and username confidential and secure from unauthorized persons.

You give permission that if there is a change of ownership of Virgin Pulse in the future, your Personal Information can be transferred to the new owner, provided that the new owner will not, in any way, limit your rights and obligations regarding the information as set out in this Privacy Policy, to the extent such information has been collected in such transfer.
